

CRISTOPHER URENA

urenacristopher2@gmail.com | 929-238-3105 | Bronx, NY 10474

Summary

experienced in helping users correct problems with computer systems, mobile devices, and peripheral equipment. Knowledgeable about usability and computer languages. Comfortable working alone to successfully investigate and troubleshoot problems. Able to create coding projects to improve users experience.

Skills

- User Support
- Hardware Diagnostics
- Customer Service
- Application Support

- Technical Troubleshooting
- Computational Design
- Python, HTML, CSS, C++,
- Payment Collection

Experience

Fordham University | Bronx, NY IT Help Desk Technician

09/2023 - Current

- Answered user inquiries to resolve computer software or hardware operation problems.
- Collaborated with technical staff to establish goals and objectives for system improvements and upgrades.
- Demonstrated advanced product knowledge to solve customer issues.
- Troubleshot hardware issues and worked with service providers to facilitate repairs for end users.

Summer Youth Employment Program | Bronx, NY

Intern

07/2023 - 08/2023

- Helped plan special events such as field trips, picnics, and BBQs.
- Supervised groups of children during recreational activities.
- Facilitated team-building exercises among different age groups of campers.
- Monitored for signs of physical and emotional distress and stopped activities to administer care when appropriate.
- Helped participants enjoy activities while ensuring adherence to protocol.

Supermarket | Bronx, NY Cashier

01/2022 - 07/2022

- Completed daily recovery tasks to keep areas clean and neat for maximum productivity.
- Established or identified prices of goods and services and tabulated bills with optical price scanners and cash registers.
- Answered customers' questions and provided information on store procedures or policies.

Education and Training

AECI 2 Charter HS | The Bronx, NY **High School Diploma** 06/2023

Fordham University | The Bronx, NY **Bachelor of Science** in Computer Science

Activities and Honors	
GymBasketballBaseballCoding	
Languages	
Spanish:	English:
Native/ Bilingual	Native/ Bilingual
Accomplishments	
CSTEP Student at Fordham University	
Certifications	

• Computer languages such as JavaScript, C++, HTML